Maryna Darashuk

https://github.com/maridoroshuk marina.doroshuk@gmail.com

Summary

I'm a self-taught (1+ year) **Front-end developer** looking for an internship or a role in an established IT company with the opportunity to work with the latest technologies on challenging and diverse projects. I'm also interested in social projects like donating platforms or data collection for monitoring and e-commers shops.

Skills

HTML & CSS, Javascript (ES5/ES6), React/Redux, MongoDB, Git

Projects

mdn/content (contribution)

Github User Search (React/Redux)

Meetup app (Next.js & MongoDB)

Certificates

React - The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux), Responsive Web Design (freecodecamp.com)

Education

Belarussian State Economic University Bachelor of analytics | 07/2020

Experience

Biznesshub

Amazon PPC Spesialist | 06/2021 - Present

- Setting up and managing Amazon Ad campaigns, ad groups, keywords, bids, and budgets (created an ad campaign with < 30% acos)
- Provide complete and accurate data in the weekly reports, developed a pivot table which made my work faster

Optidream

Amazon Account manager | 05/2020 - 06/2021

- Provide feedback from benefit buyers and other enterprise customers about customer expectations and product needs
- Made more than 5000 buyers happy with our goods providing a great product quality and customer service
- Found 3 valuable products to sell (more than 60k \$ per month profit)

ByHelp

volonteer | 09/2020 - 02/2021

- communicated with the victims and discussed what happened
- worked with Jira platform for structuring and collecting data
- processed 10+ applications per day from applicants

Languages

English (B2/C1), German (A2)